Gifford Beal
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Artwork, circa 1900-1951, Series 6:; (Boxes 2-9; OV 10, 13-20 and rolled documents 21 and 22; 3.3 linear feet)
  - Prints, circa 1900-1939 and undated, 6.3:
    - Oversized Prints (See Box 2, folders 55, 56, 58, 59) (Box 10 (OV))